A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Assistant to the Governor for Radio and Television, 1961-1965; 3; 3 Cubic Feet
  - California - General Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 935)
  - California - Interviews/Question and Answer (Box 32, Folder 936)
    Twenty-five Questions from the California Legislature.
  - California - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 937)
  - California - Trips, October 1963 (Box 32, Folder 938)
  - California - Trips, January 1964 (Box 32, Folder 939)
  - California - Trips, March 1964 (Box 32, Folder 940)
  - California - TV/Radio Programs - "The Extremists" (Box 32, Folder 941)
  - California - TV/Radio Spots - KTLA, May 19, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 942)
  - California - TV/Radio Spots - KTLA, June 1, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 943)
  - California - TV/Radio Transcripts - "The Extremists" (Box 32, Folder 944)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Advertising - General, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 945)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Handouts and Pamphlets, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 946)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Senator Ken Keating Campaign, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 947)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Box 32, Folder 948)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - NAR Position on Debates, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 949)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - New York City Republican Campaign, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 950)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Office Memoranda, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 951)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - "Rockefeller for President," Maine (Box 33, Folder 952)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - "Rockefeller for President" Press Releases (Box 33, Folder 953)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - Schedules, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 954)
  - Campaign Materials, 1960-1965 - West Coast Campaign Materials, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 955)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Contracts - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 956)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Cost Transfer Forms, blank (Box 33, Folder 957)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Miscellaneous, (A-Z) (Box 33, Folder 958)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - All Service Film Laboratories, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 959)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Bonded Film Storage (Box 33, Folder 960)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Florman & Babb, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 961)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Gotham Recording Committee (Box 33, Folder 962)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Imero Fiorentino Associates (Box 33, Folder 963)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - K&W Film Service Corporation (Box 33, Folder 964)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - MGM Telestudios, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 965)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - MOR -Soundtracks, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 966)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Plaza Sound Studios, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 967)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Q-TV, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 968)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Reeves Sound Studios (Box 33, Folder 969)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Ross-Gaffney, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 970)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Sandale Productions, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 971)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Invoices - Videotape Productions of New York, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 972)
  - Forms/Contracts/Invoices - Supply of Materials Forms, (A-Z) (Box 33, Folder 973)
  - General Correspondence - Appointments Office File, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 974)
  - General Correspondence - General (A-Z) (Box 34, Folder 975)
  - General Correspondence - Lukens, D.E. "Buz" (Box 34, Folder 976)
  - General Correspondence - MGM Telestudios, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 977)
  - General Correspondence - Movietone News (Box 34, Folder 978)
  - General Correspondence - National Broadcasting Company (Box 34, Folder 979)
  - General Correspondence - Wycoff, Gene (Box 34, Folder 980)
  - Interviews - "Firestone Interview," Palm Springs, California (Box 34, Folder 981)
  - Interviews - "The Making of a President - 1960" (Box 34, Folder 982)
  - Interviews - On Civil Rights, July 31, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 983)
  - Interviews - "Meet the Press", September 15, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 984)
  - Interviews - "The Loyal Opposition", September 16, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 985)
  - Interviews - French Broadcasting System, September 17, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 986)
  - Interviews - "Issues and Answers", October 27, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 987)
  - Interviews - "Face the Nation", November 17, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 988)
  - Interviews - "Governor Rockefeller Interviewed", January 17, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 989)
  - Interviews - "Governor Rockefeller Interviewed on Red China," CBS News, January 27, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 990)
  - Interviews - "Issues and Answers", February 16, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 991)
  - Interviews - "Face the Nation", March 8, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 992)
  - Memoranda - Moore, Charles (Box 34, Folder 993)
  - Memoranda - Swicker, Richard K. (Box 34, Folder 994)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Advertising (Box 34, Folder 995)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Brandt Enos Associates, Producer (Box 34, Folder 996)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Final Revised Edition Transcript (Box 34, Folder 997)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Narration Scripts, voice overs (Box 34, Folder 998)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Nebraska Edition (Box 34, Folder 999)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - Pre-production Scripts (Box 35, Folder 1000)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - South and Southwest Distribution (Box 35, Folder 1001)
  - "The Nelson Rockefeller Story" - West Virginia Edition (Box 35, Folder 1002)
  - New Hampshire - Appearances, November 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1003)
    Candidacy announcement
  - New Hampshire - Correspondence/Memoranda (Box 35, Folder 1004)
  - New Hampshire - Debates (Box 35, Folder 1005)
  - New Hampshire - Finances (Box 35, Folder 1006)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, December 31, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1007)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, January 16, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1008)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, January 25, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1009)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, February 12-14, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1010)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, February 19-23, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1011)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, February 24-29, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1012)
  - New Hampshire - Remarks/Speeches/Releases, March 2-9, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1013)
  - New Hampshire - Trips, October 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1014)
  - New Hampshire - Trips, November 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1015)
  - New Hampshire - Trips, January 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1016)
  - New Hampshire - Trips, March 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1017)
  - New Hampshire - TV/Radio Programs - French Language Commercial (Box 35, Folder 1018)
    With notation in NAR's hand, "not used."
  - New Hampshire - TV/Radio Programs - Manchester, New Hampshire, March 9, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1019)
  - New Hampshire - TV/Radio Programs - "Meet Nelson Rockefeller", March 9, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1020)
  - New York - "A Working Capital for New York State - A Presentation of the South Mall Plan" (Box 35, Folder 1021)
  - New York - NAR Inaugural, January 1, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1022)
  - New York - Newspapers in New York State (Box 35, Folder 1023)
  - New York - New York State Republican Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 1024)
  - New York - Press Conference, 2/22/63 (Box 35, Folder 1025)
  - New York - World Trade Center Function, October 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1026)
  - Oregon - Appearances in Eugene, October 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1027)
  - Oregon - Bills/Invoices (Box 36, Folder 1028)
  - Oregon - Trips, February 6-8, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1029)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Programs - Final Shows (Box 36, Folder 1030)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Programs - Lloyd Center, Oregon taping (Box 36, Folder 1031)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Programs - "The People Speak" (Box 36, Folder 1032)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Programs - "Ring Rockefeller" (Box 36, Folder 1033)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Programs - "Rockefeller Telethon" (Box 36, Folder 1034)
  - Oregon - TV/Radio Schedules (Box 36, Folder 1035)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Highway Needs and Fees, January 31, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1036)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - "Mr. Lincoln's Party Today", February 26, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1037)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - "A Matter of Principle", July 14, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1038)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Bronfman Prize Announcement, October 16, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1039)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - U.S. Foreign Policy, November 16, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1040)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Post-mourning message, December 23, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1041)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Mansion Art Tour, taping, January 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1042)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Annual Message, January 8, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1043)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - New Hampshire Commercials, January 22, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1044)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - "Report to the People", February 14, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1045)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Liquor Law Reform, April 7, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1046)
  - Speeches, Statements, and Tapings - Latin America, April 21, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1047)
  - Trips - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, March 9, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1048)
  - Trips - Kansas and Nebraska, April 5-7, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1049)
  - Trips - Cincinnati, Ohio, April 29, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1050)
  - Trips - Illinois, September 7, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1051)
  - Trips - Virginia and West Virginia, September 21-22, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1052)
  - Trips - Brussels, Belgium, October 1-2, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1053)
  - Trips - Miami, Florida, November 13, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1054)
  - Trips - Washington, DC, January 9-11, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1055)
  - Trips - Boston, Massachusetts, January 20-25, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1056)
  - Trips - Republican National Convention, San Francisco, California, July 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1057)
  - TV/Radio - Coverage Reports - New Hampshire, October 18-19, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1058)
  - TV/Radio - Coverage Reports - West Coast, October 22, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1059)
  - TV/Radio - Coverage Reports - Candidacy Announcement, November 6-8, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1060)
  - TV/Radio - Coverage Reports - Missouri, November 15-17, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1061)
  - NOT USED (Box 37, Folder 1062)
  - TV/Radio - Reference Materials - Area Coverage Maps, New Hampshire (Box 37, Folder 1063)
  - TV/Radio - Reference Materials - Broadcasters and Station Managers, New York State (Box 37, Folder 1064)
  - TV/Radio - Reference Materials - Clippings/Articles on Federal Communications Commission (FCC) (Box 37, Folder 1065)
  - TV/Radio - Reference Materials - Insurance Floaters (Box 37, Folder 1066)
  - TV/Radio - Reference Materials - LOGOS Mobile TV Unit (Box 37, Folder 1067)
  - TV/Radio - Schedules - Mayor's Day, May 22, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1068)
  - TV/Radio - Schedules - Schedule of TV and Radio Spots, 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 37, Folder 1069)
  - TV/Radio - Schedules - Schedule of TV and Radio Spots, 1962 Gubernatorial Campaign (Box 37, Folder 1070)
  - TV/Radio - Schedules - Tele-tape Productions, Inc., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1071)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Education Booklet Offer, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1072)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Available One-Minute Radio and TV Spots, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1073)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Radio Spots, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 1074)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Series A, January 19, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1075)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Series B, February 11, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1076)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Series C, February 26, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1077)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Television Spots, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 1078)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Louis Lefkowitz, John Lomenzo, Malcolm Wilson, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 1079)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - Spots - Senator Thomas Kuchel on NAR and Foreign Policy for California Primary, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1080)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Executive Chamber" - "How Much Education?", November 16, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1081)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Executive Chamber #2" - "Little Drops of Water", December 11, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1082)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Executive Chamber" - "In the Name of the People", December 28, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1083)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Executive Chamber" - Labor Film, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1084)
    Excerpts of NAR speeches used by Vic Borella in film for labor groups.
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Pay As You Go", June 29, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1085)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "New York State's Minimum Wage Law", July 6, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1086)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "New York's Narcotics Problem", July 13, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1087)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "School Integration", July 20, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1088)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Mandatory Health Insurance", July 27, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1089)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Commuter Transportation", August 3, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1090)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Strikes Against the Government", August 10, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1091)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Free Tuition", August 17, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1092)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Marriage Counseling Regulation", August 31, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1093)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Taxation Independence for New York City", September 21, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1094)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Control of Firearms", January 5, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1095)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Legislative Hearing" - "Grand Jury Presentments", February 16, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 1096)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Rockefeller Gets Warm Reception in Midwest," NBC, September 2, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1097)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "The Republican Record", 1962? (Box 39, Folder 1098)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Rockefeller's Way", 1964 (Box 39, Folder 1099)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Rocky for President", 1964 (Box 39, Folder 1100)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - School Prayer Message, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 1101)
  - TV/Radio - Transcripts - "Stay in School" Message, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 1102)
- George Hinman and Ilene Slater Files, 1959-1962; 4; 6 Cubic Feet
  The subseries is broken into two parts: State Files and Subject Files. The files are arranged alphabetically.
  George Hinman and Ilene Slater were executive assistants to Governor Rockefeller. In 1959, they were assigned the responsibility of exploring Governor Rockefeller's chances of winning the Republican presidential nomination in 1960. For the most part, these files cover the period from late 1959 to early 1960. Some items are dated as late as 1962.
  The State Files include such information as the names of each state's government officials; a list of delegates to the 1956 Republican Convention; correspondence with supporters of Governor Rockefeller; invitations to speak to groups of supporters; schedules for trips; thank you letters; and clippings. There are also files for the District of Columbia, Guam, Puerto Rico, and the U.S. Virgin Islands. Within the Subject Files is correspondence with supporters and groups seeking to draft Governor Rockefeller; memoranda; and notices and reports regarding different phases of the 1960 campaign. At the end of this section are several files dealing specifically with the 1960 Republican Convention. (In his capacity as a Republican National Committeeman, Mr. Hinman was involved in the process of choosing delegates to the nominating conventions.) Within these files is one entitled "Convention Speeches" containing Governor Rockefeller's handwritten copy of his speech nominating Richard Nixon as the Republican presidential candidate.
  Also included in this subseries is George Hinman's "Talent File." This consists of approximately 300 blue 3" x 5" index cards. On each card is the name and address of an individual and a brief description of that person's talents, experience, contacts, and sometimes another person's opinion of that individual. Many of the cards are dated indicating that this file was created in 1962 and 1963. An undated note at the beginning of the file reads, "Not useful at present - return to Ilene [Slater]." The Talent File is in Box 21 at the end of the series.
  - State Files - Alabama (Box 39, Folder 1103)
  - State Files - Alaska (Box 39, Folder 1104)
  - State Files - Arizona (Box 39, Folder 1105)
  - State Files - Arkansas (Box 39, Folder 1106)
  - State Files - California, June-August 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1107)
  - State Files - California, September-October 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1108)
  - State Files - California, November 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1109)
  - State Files - California - Supplementary, November 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1110)
  - State Files - California, December 1959 (Box 40, Folder 1111)
  - State Files - California, January-March 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1112)
  - State Files - California, April-May 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1113)
  - State Files - California, June 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1114)
  - State Files - California, July 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1115)
  - State Files - California - Clippings File (Box 40, Folder 1116)
  - State Files - California - Invitations (Box 41, Folder 1117)
  - State Files - California - Thank You Letters (Box 41, Folder 1118)
  - State Files - Colorado (Box 41, Folder 1119)
  - State Files - Connecticut (Box 41, Folder 1120)
  - State Files - Delaware (Box 41, Folder 1121)
  - State Files - District of Columbia, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 1122)
  - State Files - District of Columbia, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 1123)
  - State Files - Florida, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 1124)
  - State Files - Florida, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 1125)
  - State Files - Georgia (Box 42, Folder 1126)
  - State Files - Guam, U.S. Territory (Box 42, Folder 1127)
  - State Files - Hawaii (Box 42, Folder 1128)
  - State Files - Idaho (Box 42, Folder 1129)
  - State Files - Illinois, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 1130)
  - State Files - Illinois, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 1131)
  - State Files - Indiana (Box 42, Folder 1132)
  - State Files - Iowa (Box 43, Folder 1133)
  - State Files - Kansas (Box 43, Folder 1134)
  - State Files - Kentucky (Box 43, Folder 1135)
  - State Files - Louisiana (Box 43, Folder 1136)
  - State Files - Maine (Box 43, Folder 1137)
  - State Files - Maryland (Box 43, Folder 1138)
  - State Files - Massachusetts, December 1958-October 1959 (Box 43, Folder 1139)
  - State Files - Massachusetts, October 1959 - October 1960 (Box 43, Folder 1140)
  - State Files - Michigan (Box 43, Folder 1141)
  - State Files - Minnesota (Box 44, Folder 1142)
  - State Files - Mississippi (Box 44, Folder 1143)
  - State Files - Missouri (Box 44, Folder 1144)
  - State Files - Montana (Box 44, Folder 1145)
  - State Files - Nebraska (Box 44, Folder 1146)
  - State Files - Nevada (Box 44, Folder 1147)
  - State Files - New Hampshire, June-September 1959 (Box 44, Folder 1148)
  - State Files - New Hampshire, October 1959 - July 1960 (Box 44, Folder 1149)
  - State Files - New Hampshire - Thank You Letters (Box 44, Folder 1150)
  - State Files - New Jersey, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 1151)
  - State Files - New Jersey, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1152)
  - State Files - New Mexico (Box 45, Folder 1153)
  - State Files - New York, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1154)
  - State Files - New York, January-April 1960 (Box 45, Folder 1155)
  - State Files - New York, May-June 1960 (Box 45, Folder 1156)
  - State Files - New York, July-November 1960 (Box 46, Folder 1157)
  - State Files - New York - Thank You Letters (Box 46, Folder 1158)
  - State Files - North Carolina (Box 46, Folder 1159)
  - State Files - North Dakota (Box 46, Folder 1160)
  - State Files - Ohio (Box 46, Folder 1161)
  - State Files - Oklahoma (Box 46, Folder 1162)
  - State Files - Oregon (Box 46, Folder 1163)
  - State Files - Pennsylvania, June 1959 - June 1960 (Box 46, Folder 1164)
  - State Files - Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1165)
  - State Files - Puerto Rico, U.S. Commonwealth (Box 47, Folder 1166)
  - State Files - Rhode Island, May 1959 - March 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1167)
  - State Files - Rhode Island, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1168)
  - State Files - South Carolina (Box 47, Folder 1169)
  - State Files - South Dakota (Box 47, Folder 1170)
  - State Files - Tennessee (Box 47, Folder 1171)
  - State Files - Texas, July 1959 - June 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1172)
  - State Files - Texas, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1173)
  - State Files - U.S. Virgin Islands, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1174)
  - State Files - Utah (Box 47, Folder 1175)
  - State Files - Vermont, July 1959 - June 1960 (Box 47, Folder 1176)
  - State Files - Vermont, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1177)
  - State Files - Vermont - Thank You Letters (Box 47, Folder 1178)
  - State Files - Virginia (Box 48, Folder 1179)
  - State Files - Washington, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 1180)
  - State Files - Washington - Invitations (Box 48, Folder 1181)
  - State Files - West Virginia (Box 48, Folder 1182)
  - State Files - Wisconsin, April - October 1959 (Box 48, Folder 1183)
  - State Files - Wisconsin, October 1959 - November 1960 (Box 48, Folder 1184)
  - State Files - Wyoming (Box 48, Folder 1185)
  - Subject Files - Brinton, William A. (Box 48, Folder 1186)
    California lawyer helping to secure Northern California support for NAR.
  - Subject Files - Campaign Files - Finances (Box 49, Folder 1187)
  - Subject Files - Campaign Files - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 1188)
  - Subject Files - Campaign Files - Sample Literature and Handouts (Box 49, Folder 1189)
  - Subject Files - Campbell, General Thomas D. (Box 49, Folder 1190)
    New Mexico what farmer, pro-NAR
  - Subject Files - Carter, John (Box 49, Folder 1191)
    Maryland
  - Subject Files - "Citizens for Rockefeller" (Box 49, Folder 1192)
    Public interest groups seeking to draft NAR in 1960
  - Subject Files - "College Groups" (Box 49, Folder 1193)
    Students supporting NAR
  - Subject Files - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1194)
    List of Salutations used by George L. Hinman and letters sent
  - Subject Files - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1195)
    Thank you letters, NAR acknowledges supporters of "Citizens for Rockefeller"
  - Subject Files - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1196)
    Thank you letters, miscellaneous
  - Subject Files - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1197)
  - Subject Files - "Draft Rockefeller" (Box 50, Folder 1198)
    National movement to draft NAR
  - Subject Files - General Files, Hinman, George L. (Box 50, Folder 1199)
  - Subject Files - Halpern, Alexander (Box 50, Folder 1200)
    New York lawyer, headed "Citizens for Rockefeller"
  - Subject Files - Intelligence Summary as of August 17, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 1201)
  - Subject Files - Javits, Senator Jacob K. (Box 50, Folder 1202)
  - Subject Files - Keating, Senator Kenneth B. (Box 50, Folder 1203)
  - Subject Files - Labor (Box 50, Folder 1204)
    Mostly from Vic Borella, Executive Vice President of Rockefeller Center, Inc.
  - Subject Files - Losee, Thomas P. (Box 50, Folder 1205)
    Research assistant
  - Subject Files - Malone, George W. (Box 50, Folder 1206)
    Managing Director of Industrial West Foundation
  - Subject Files - Mass Solicitation (Box 50, Folder 1207)
    New York State Republican Party Test mailing, with sample letters
  - Subject Files - McMicking, Joseph R. (Box 50, Folder 1208)